<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>China Post Online - China News</title>
<copyright>Copyright (c) 2007 The China Post All rights reserved.</copyright>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china</link>
<description>Taiwan's leading English-language newspaper since 1952. The China Post Online is the leading online provider of news and business and entertainment information on Taiwan.</description>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 09:50:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
<language>zh-TW</language><image>
<title>China Post > China</title>
<url>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/rss/images/china_post.gif</url>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china</link>
</image>
<item>
<title>11 missing in east China after building collapses</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306868/11-missing.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - State media say rescuers are searching for 11 workers who were buried when an office building they were renovating in eastern China collapsed on top of them.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306868/11-missing.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 23:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vietnamese protest China for 3rd week</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306846/Vietnamese-protest.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - Hundreds of Vietnamese launched a third week of protests against China on Sunday amid escalating tensions in disputed waters of the South China Sea, where both countries recently conducted live-fire military drills.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306846/Vietnamese-protest.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 23:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Chinese copy of Austrian village stirs emotions</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306835/Chinese-copy.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - It's a scenic jewel, a hamlet of hill-hugging chalets, elegant church spires and ancient inns all reflected in the deep still waters of an Alpine lake. Hallstatt's beauty has earned it a listing as a UNESCO World Heritage site but some villagers are less happy about a more recent distinction: plans to copy their hamlet in China.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306835/Chinese-copy.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 22:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Shanghai releases plan for health care reform</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/local-news/shanghai/2011/06/20/306786/Shanghai-releases.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - The municipality of Shanghai kicked off a week-long debate on its draft plan to reform its medical and drug system, posting the plan online on Wednesday for public comment.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/local-news/shanghai/2011/06/20/306786/Shanghai-releases.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 21:04:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stocks losing their luster in US markets amid allegations of accounting fraud</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/business/2011/06/20/306787/Stocks-losing.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - High-flying shares in Chinese companies have come crashing to the ground recently, amid a flurry of accounting scandals and a crackdown by U.S. regulators.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/business/2011/06/20/306787/Stocks-losing.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 21:04:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sinopec plans new refinery complex</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/business/2011/06/20/306785/Sinopec-plans.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - China Petroleum and Chemical Corp, the country's biggest refiner by capacity, is planning to build a refining complex with an annual processing capacity of 32 million tons in China's eastern Jiangsu province.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/business/2011/06/20/306785/Sinopec-plans.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 21:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Beijing, Shanghai sit at top of well-being index</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306784/Beijing-Shanghai.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - Beijing, Shanghai and Tianjin topped the charts of a well-being index that is part of an academic report released on Saturday.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306784/Beijing-Shanghai.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 21:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Over 2 mil. affected by flooding in eastern Zhejiang: state media</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/local-news/other/2011/06/20/306783/Over-2.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - More than 2 million people have been displaced or otherwise affected by flooding in eastern China's Zhejiang province that is also pushing up food prices, state media reported Sunday.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/local-news/other/2011/06/20/306783/Over-2.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 21:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Property prices in many cities still rising: survey</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306782/Property-prices.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - The price of new apartments rose in May in 67 out of 70 Chinese cities tracked in a monthly survey, the National Bureau of Statistics said Saturday, as the government battles to rein in inflation.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306782/Property-prices.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 21:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Import growth will 'probably' slow down: official</title>
<link>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306781/Import-growth.htm</link>
<description>(ChinaPost.com.tw) - China's import growth will “probably” slow down in the months ahead as the government's measures to cool the economy take off, and the prospects for exports are not optimistic, said Zhong Shan, the country's vice-minister of commerce.
</description>
<guid>http://www.chinapost.com.tw/china/national-news/2011/06/20/306781/Import-growth.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 20:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>